Guide to the Professor William C. Moffit Papers
University of Houston Libraries
- Original Moffit Working Scores
  - “Take Me Out to the Ball Game”, April 6, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - “Taps II” (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - “Ta Ra Ra Boom” (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - “T-Bones ‘76” (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - “T.C.U. Fanfare” (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - “Tea for Two”; Tubas, October 1963 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - “Tell Me Why”; No. 4 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - “Tell Me Why”; original (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - “Tennessee” (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - “Texas” (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - “Texas Our Texas”, July 26, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - “Temptation”, February 9, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - “That’s Entertainment”, March 2, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - "That Old Black Magic II”, October 23, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - “That Old Black Magic III” (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - “That’s A Plenty” (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - “That’ll Be the Day” (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - “The 500” (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - “The Desert Fiend” (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - “The Glow-Worm” (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - “The Horse” (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - “The Masterpiece”, February 20, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - “The Power of God” (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - “The Spirit is Willing” (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - “The Stars and Stripes Forever March” (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - “The Stripper” (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - “Themes From the Nutcracker Suite” (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - “Nutcracker Suite II” (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - “There’s No Business Like Show Business”, November 1963 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - “They’re Playing My Song” (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - “This Could Be the Start of Something” (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - “This is Your Land” (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - “This is Your Land II” (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - “Three Coins”; October 29, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - “Tiger Rag” (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - “Tiger Rag II’, December 15, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - “Tijuana Fight Song” (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - “Tijuana Taxi” (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - “Today’s Top Hits” (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - “Tonight” (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - “Top of the World” (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - “Toot-Toot Tootsie” (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - “Top of the Heap” (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - “Toy Soldiers” (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - “Trojans One and All” (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - “Trolley Song” (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - “Trumpet Boogie” (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - “Tulane” (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - “Tulsa” (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - "Twelfth St. Rag” (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - “Twenty-First Century” (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - “Two Guitars” (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - “U.C. Fanfare” (Intros); “U.C. Fight Song” (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - “U.C.L.A.” (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - “U.C.L.A. Fanfare”, August 31, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - “U.N.F. Alma Mater” (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - “Up and Down the Monon” (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - “Up on the Housetop” (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - “Up, Up and Away”, November 10, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - “University of Houston Alma Mater and Fight Song” (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - “University of Utah” (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - “Utah” (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - “Varsity Drag”, October 1962 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - “Vehicle” (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - “Vermont” (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - “Vibrato Studies I” (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - “Victors” (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - “Victory March”, June 10, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - “Victory March II”, October 17, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - “Victory Song”; W. Laf. (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - “Villanova” (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - “Virginia” (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Vocal Part Masters (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - V.T.S. Music (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - “V.W. Miller Fight Song” (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - “Wabash Blues” (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - “Made in the Water” (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - “Waiting for Robert E. Lee” (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - “Wake Forest” (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - “Wander Indiana”; August 25, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - “War Eagle”; (Auburn) (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - “Washington” (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - “Washington and Lee Fanfare” (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - “Washington and Lee Swing”; August 21, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - “Washington and Lee Swing”; Page 1-Page 2 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - “Washington: Behind Closed Doors”; February 10, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - “Washington Square” (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - “Wassail Song”, August 25, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - “Wave the Flag” (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - “Wedding March” (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - “We Three Kings”, August 12, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - “We Will Rock You” (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - “We Wish You A Merry Christmas” (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - “Well Git It II” (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - “We’re Marching on College Song” (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - “West Campus Fight Song”, October 7, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - “Westside Story” (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - “West Texas State” (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - “West Virginia” (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - “What Child is This?”, October 4, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - “Wheaties” (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - “Whipped Cream”, February 11, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - “Wisconsin” (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - “Whistle Cheer” (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - “Wildcat Victory” (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - “William Tell” (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - “Winds of War: March and Love Theme” (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - “Witchcraft” (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - “Woodchoppers Ball” (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - “Work Song”, November 14, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - “Work Song II” (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - “Work Song March” (Box 23, Folder 60)
  - “Wrigley Spearmint Gum” (Box 23, Folder 61)
  - “Wyoming” (Box 23, Folder 62)
  - “Yea Alabama”, October 23, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 63)
  - “Yellow and Blue (Pirate’s Chorus) Balfe” (Box 23, Folder 64)
  - “Yellow Rose of Texas” (Box 23, Folder 65)
  - “Yellow Rose of Texas II”, November 12, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 66)
  - “Yellow Submarine” (Box 23, Folder 67)
  - “Yes Sir, That’s My Baby”, September 1960 (Box 23, Folder 68)
  - “You’re a Grand Old Flag” (Box 23, Folder 69)
  - “You’re Just in Love”, October 1963 (Box 23, Folder 70)
  - “Zing Went the Strings of My Heart”, October 1960 (Box 23, Folder 71)
  - "Can-Can" (Ovs box 61, Folder 9)
  - "Betty Co-Ed" (Ovs box 61, Folder 10)
  - "Finger Busters" (Ovs box 61, Folder 11)
  - "Rampart" (Ovs box 61, Folder 12)
  - "Olympic Fanfare and Theme" (Ovs box 61, Folder 13)
  - "Stars and Stripes" (Ovs box 61, Folder 14)
  - "Texas" (Ovs box 61, Folder 15)
  - "The Trolley Song" (Ovs box 61, Folder 16)
  - "Care and Feeding of the Band Musician"; Concert Band Calisthenics (Ovs box 61, Folder 17)
  - "Concert Opener" (Ovs box 61, Folder 18)
  - "Hi Tech for Middle School Concert Band" (Ovs box 61, Folder 19)
  - "Middle School Calisthenics"; page 1-23 (Ovs box 61, Folder 20)
  - "Untitled" (Ovs box 61, Folder 21)
- Moffit's Published Arrangements
  This series contains 9 boxes of Moffit’s published arrangements and the series is organized into four sub-series: Moffit’s arrangements and scores, Soundpower’s Greatest Hits, “Christmas Celebration,” and “”Special Occasions”. Additional published arrangements can be found in Series 17, Jacksonville Community Band Materials. Materials are arranged alphabetically. Original folder and item order has been maintained whenever possible. Exceptions were made when folders were obviously misfiled or when no order was apparent.
  - Moffit Arrangements and Scores
    This sub-series contains 8 boxes of published arrangements by Bill Moffit, most of which were publish by Hal Leonard Music, Inc. Many of the arrangements are part of the Moffit’s Soundpower or Showpower series. Materials are arranged alphabetically. Original folder and item order has been maintained whenever possible. Exceptions were made when folders were obviously misfiled or when no order was apparent.
    - "ABC Monday Night Football” (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - "Across the Field" (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - "Action Fanfares No.1, No.2, No.3" (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - "Ain't No Woman" (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - "Alexander's Ragtime Band" (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - "All I Ever Need is You" (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - "Alley Cat" (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - "America the Beautiful" (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - "American the Beatiful – Taps" (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - "Another Op'nin, Another Show" (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - "April in Paris" (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - "Auld Lang Syne" (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - "Auld Lang Syne (Farewell)" (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - "Bach with a Beat" (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - "Back Home Again, In Indiana" (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - "Basin Street Blues" (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - "Battle Hymn of the Republic" (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - "Baubles, Bangles, and Beads" (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - "Beer Barrel Polka" (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - "Begin the Beuine - (March)" (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - "The Best of the Boss" (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - "Big Spender" (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - "Bill Bailey's Combo" (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - "Bill Bailey's Stomp" (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - "Birthday Chorale and March" (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - "B.J. McKay" (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - "Boogie Blues" (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - "Boogie Down" (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - "Medley of Budweiser Songs" (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - "Burgler's Dream" (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - "But Not For Me" (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - "Brazil" (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - "The Caisson Song" (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - "California Dreamin'" (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - "Calling Occupants of Interplanetary Craft" (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - "Campus Chimes and Alma Mater" (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - "Can Can" (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - "Car Wash" (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - "The Care and Feeding of the Band Musician (One Minute Marching Band Calisthenics)” (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - "Carioca" (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - "Carry the Big Fresh Flavor" (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - "Cecilia" (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - "Charleston" (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - "Cheerleader Strut (Our Boys Will Shine" (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - "Circus Entry – Traditional" (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - "Classic Miniatures" (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - "Classical Cheers" (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - "Cohan Salute" (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - "Comedians' Gallup" (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - "Conquest Entry" (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - "Cotton Eyed Joe" (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - "Cumana" (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - "Cute" (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - "Dancing in the Dark" (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - "Different Worlds" (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - "Discover America" (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - "Do Lord" (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - "Don't Fence Me In" (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - "Don't Let the Sun Go Down on Me" (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - "Doublemint Will Do It" (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - "Drill Music for Patterns of Motion" (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - "Duel" Conductors (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - "Dynamic Drums" (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - "Ear Poppin' Fanfares" (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - "España Cani” (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - "Eli's Coming" (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - "El Cumanchero” (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - "The Entertainer" (From the motion picture “The Sting”) (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - "Everything's Coming Up Roses" (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - "Ezekiel" (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - "Fanfare for 'Rocky'" (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - "Feelin' Stronger Every Day" (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - "Festival Fanfare and March" (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - "Fever" (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - "Fight On" (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - "Fire and Rain" (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - "Five Days from Home" (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - "Five Foot Two, Eyes of Blue (Has Anybody Seen My Girl?)” (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - "Flashdance...What a Feeling" (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - "Free" (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - "From this Moment On" (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - "Front and Center" (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - "Get Ready" (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - "Girl Talk" (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - "Great Gate" (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - "Go Northwestern Go (Go U Northwestern) (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - "God Bless America" (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - "Goofus" (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - "Granada" (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - "Grandioso" (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - "Green Onions" (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - "Hail to Thee – Annie Lisle (Alma Mater)” (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - "Hail Purdue" (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - "Have a Coke and a Smile" (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - "Hawaiian War Chant" (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - "Heartbreaker" (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - "Hello Dolly" (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - "Here Comes the King" (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - "Hernando's Hideaway" (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - "Hey, Look Me Over" (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - "Hi-Tech" (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - "Homecoming Ceremony" (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - "Hoosier Pride" (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - "The Horse" (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - "Hurdles & Girdles" (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - "I Got Rhythm" (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - "I Only Want to be With You" (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - "I Love a Parade" (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - "I Love Paris" (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - "I'd Like to Teach the World to Sing" (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - "If My Friends Could See Me Now" (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - "If You Leave" (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - "Illinois Loyalty (We're Loyal to You, Illinois)" (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - "I'm a Brass Band" (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - "Intermission Riff" (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - "It's So Easy" (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - "It's Still Rock and Roll to Me" (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - "Jazz Me Blues" (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - "Johnny One Note" (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - "Johnson Rag" (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - "Joshua" (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - "Joy" (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - "Just One of Those Things" (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - "Karma Chameleon" (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - "Kind of a Woman" (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - "Knock on Wood" (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - "Language of Love" (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - "Lassus Trombone" (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - "Latin Prelude" (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - "Lazy River" (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - "Lennon/McCartney Hits" (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - "Lightly" (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - "Life is a Song Worth Singing" (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - "Little Boat" (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - "Live and Let Die" (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - "Lover" (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - "Lullaby of Broadway" (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - "Macarena" (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - "Major Tom (Coming Home)" (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - "Man With the Golden Arm" (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - "Malaguena" (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - "Mame" (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - "Manhattan Skyline" (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - "March America" (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - "The Masterpiece" (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - "The Mexican Suffle" (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - "Mickey Mouse March" (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - "Midnight Sun" (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - "Mississippi Mud" (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - "Misty" (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - "Monday, Monday" (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - "Money, Money, Money" (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - "Moonlight Serenade" (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - "Muppet Medley" (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - "Music! Music! Music!" (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - "Musical Cheers" (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - "Musical Cocktail" (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - "Muskrat Ramble" (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - "My Life" (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - "The Name of the Game" (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - "Night Train' (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - "Not Fragile" (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - "Not from Dixie" (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - "Notre Dame Victory March" (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - "O' Canada" (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - "Ode to Billy Joe (Disco)" (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - "Oh, Babe, What Would You Say?" (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - "Ol' Man River" (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - "On the Radio" (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - "On the Shelf" (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - "On Wisconsin" (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - "Once in Love with Amy" (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - "One" (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - "Onward Christian Soldiers" (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - "Operator" (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - "Overture 1812" (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - "Oye Negra" (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - "Parade of the Tin Soldiers" (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - "The Peanut Vendor" (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - "Pink Panther" (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - "The Power of Gold" (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - "Reach Out" (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - "Road Runner Theme" (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - "Rock-A-Bye Your Baby" (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - "Rock-A-Bye Your Baby (With Dixie Melody)" (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - "Round and Round" (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - "The Rubberband Man" (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - "Saints in Concert" (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - "San Antonio Rose" (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - "Saturday Night" (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - "See the U.S.A. (In Your Chevrolet)" (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - "September" (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - "Seventy Six Trombones" (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - "Shangrilla" (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - "Should I Do It" (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - "'Show Biz' Chasers and Tags" (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - "Show Fanfares" (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - "Showcase for Band" (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - "Silverado" (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - "Sing, Sing, Sing" (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - "Sky High" (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - "Slaughter of Tenth Avenue" (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - "Something for Cat" (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - "The Sound of Music" (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - "Soundpower Fanfares" (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - "Soundpower's Greatest Rock Hits" (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - "South" (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - "South Rampart Street Parade" (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - "Special Events Music - Chorales" (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - "St. Elmo's Fire (Man in Motion)" (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - "Stardust" (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - "Fanfare and The Star Spangled Banner" (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - "The Stars and Stripes Finale" (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - "Stars and Stripes Trio" (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - "Stranger in Paradise" (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - "Strike up the Band" (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - "The Stripper" (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - "Superstar" (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - "Sugar Blues" (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - "Swanee" (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - "Sweet Georgia Brown - (Rock)" (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - "Swing Low Sweet Chariot" (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - "The Tailgate Ramble (On Parade)" (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - "Ta-Ra-Ra-Boom" (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - "Tea for Two" (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - "Tea for Two for Tappers / Tea for Two for Tubas" (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - "Temptation" (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - "Texas" (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - "Texas Our Texas" (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - "That Old Black Magic" (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - "That's Entertainment" (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - "Theme from Raging Bull" (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - "They Just Can't Stop It (The Games People Play)" (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - "This is My Country" (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - "This Land is Your Land" (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - "Tiger Rag (Hold That Tiger)" (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - "Tonight" (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - "Toot Toot Tootsie" (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - "The Trolley Song" (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - "Top of the Heap" (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - "TSOP (The Sound of Philadelphia)" (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - "Tu-Ba or not Tu-Ba" (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - "Up, Up and Away" (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - "Up in a Puff of Smoke" (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - "Varsity Drag" (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - "Wabash Blues" (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - "Wabash Cannonball" (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - "Washington Behind Closed Doors" (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - "Well, Git It!" (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - "Whatever Lola Wants (Lola Gets)" (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - "When Johnny Comes Marching Home" (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - "When Johnny Comes Marching Home" (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - "Wheel of Fortune" (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - "Wildcat Victory" (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - "The Winds of War" (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - "The Winner Takes All" (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - "Witchcraft" (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - "Woodchopper's Ball" (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - "The Work Song March" (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - "Yellow Submarine" (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - "Yes Indeed!" (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - "(I Wonder Why?) You're Just in Love" (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - "You've Said it All" (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - "Zing! Went the Strings of My Heart" (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Soundpower's Greatest Hits
    This sub-series contains 20 folders of published arrangements by Bill Moffit from Soundpower’s Greatest Hits, publish by Hal Leonard Publishing Corporation. This collection of popular titles contains some of his most requested arrangements. Materials include the conductor’s score and parts for all the marching band instruments. Materials are arranged alphabetically.
    - 1st B♭ Clarinet (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - 1st B♭ Cornet (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - 1st Trombone (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - 2nd B♭ Clarinet (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - 2nd B♭ Cornet (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - 2nd Trombone (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - 3 Pitch Drums (Timp-Toms) (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - 3rd B♭ Cornet (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - 4 Pitch Drums (Bongos-Timbales) (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - B♭ Tenor Saxophone (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - Baritone B.C. (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - Baritone T.C. (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - Basses (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - C Part (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - Conductor (Box 31, Folder 40)
    - Drums/Field Drums (Box 31, Folder 41)
    - E♭ Alto Saxophone (Box 31, Folder 42)
    - E♭ Baritone Saxophone (Box 31, Folder 43)
    - E♭ Trumpet (Box 31, Folder 44)
    - F Horn (Box 31, Folder 45)
  - "Christmas Celebrations"
    This sub-series contains 19 folders of Christmas music arrangements by Bill Moffit, publish by Hal Leonard Publishing Corporation. Materials include the conductor’s score and parts for all the band instruments. Materials are arranged alphabetically.
    - 1st B♭ Clar. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - 1st B♭ Cornet (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - 1st Trombone (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - 2nd B♭ Clar. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - 2nd B♭ Cornet (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - 2nd Trombone (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - 3rd B♭ Cornet (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - B♭ Tenor Sax. (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Baritone B.C. (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Baritone T.C. (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Basses (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - C Part (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Conductor (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - E♭ Alto Sax. (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - E♭ Bar. Sax. (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - E♭ Trumpet (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - F Horn (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Mallet Perc. (Bells & Chimes) (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Percussion (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - "Special Occassions: Band Book #1"
    This sub-series contains 22 folders of music arrangements for special occasions by Bill Moffit, publish by RBC Publications. Materials include the parts for all the band instruments. Materials are arranged alphabetically.
    - 1st Clarinet (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - 1st Cornet/Trumpet (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - 1st Trombone (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - 2nd Clarinet (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - 2nd Cornet/Trumpet (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - 2nd Trombone (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - 3rd Cornet/Trumpet (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Alto Sax. (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Bari Sax. (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Baritone B.C. (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Baritone T.C. (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Bass Clarinet (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Basses (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Bells (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - F Horn (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Field Drums (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Flute/Piccolo (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Quads (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - T-Toms (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Tenor Sax (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Vocal (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - Xylophone (Box 32, Folder 41)
- Marching Band Shows and Materials
  This series contains 8 boxes of marching band shows and clinic/instructional material created and used by William C. Moffit. Materials are arranged alphabetically and consist of 4 sub-series; Marching Band Shows, Patterns of Motion Materials, School Shows, and Miscellaneous Formations.
  - Marching Band Shows